play music
adjust stereo
open cupboards
take out measuring jug
close cupboards
pour water into measuring jug
turn off water
pick up kettle
put water in kettle
open blinds
move pot
turn off water
empty water
pour out water
put kettle down
turn on kettle
pick up pot lids
put down pot lids
turn on oven
pick up pots
place down pot on hob
pour water into pot
put down measuring jug
open fridge
take out salmon
take out kale
drop leeks
pick up leeks
open packaging
remove packaging
throw away packaging
pick up measuring jug
shake out measuring jug
put away measuring jug
pick up lids
move pans
pick up chopping block
move salmon
open leeks
put leeks in sink
throw away packaging
Wash leeks
Wash leek
Turn off tap
Shake off leeks
Shake off hands
Put leeks on chopping board
Pick up knife
Remove bottom of leek
Throw away extra leek
Chop leek
drop leek
pick up leek
rinse off leek
throw away extra leek
pick up leek
chop leek
check oven timer
pick up spoon
put down spoon
chop leek
leek
throw away leek
throw away extra leek
rinse off hands
pick up leek from floor
throw away leek
pick up kale
pick up spoon
pour water into pan
mix water
put down spoon
pick up salmon
put salmon in water
push down salmon
adjust salmon
open oven
pick up oven gloves
take out tray
put pot in oven
close oven door
set timer
pick up pot
put water in pot
pour water in kettle
turn on kettle
put pot on hub
open cupboards
put away plates
put away bowl
Put away bowl
Put away measuring cup
Put away slicer
Put away mug
Close cupboards
Check oven
Set timer
[END SUBTITLE]